Hey everybody, we are joined by Packers
general manager Brian Gutakunst. And
Gudy, it seems like you've had a busy
day. Let's see. You signed Jaden Reed to
a contract extension. You made a trade
and you drafted two players. Have you
been rather busy?
>> It's been a It's been a good day for the
Packers and um you know, yeah, our
staff's been busy. Um but um you know, I
think certainly signing Jaden and he's a
winner. He's been a great player for us.
Um that was really exciting to start the
day off and then at the beginning of the
draft finally get a pick, you know,
after missing yesterday and getting two
players that um you know I really really
like, our staff really likes, our
coaching staff likes and uh and and we
think they're going to be really good
Packers.
>> Talking about those two players, Brennan
Cece,
>> corner out of South Carolina. What
really attracted you to him?
>> Yeah, he's got you he's almost six feet.
Uh he's got good length, really good
feet, excellent transition quickness. Uh
he can run. Uh he's very aggressive and
competitive and I think that's that's
what drew us to him. We started at NC
State, was a really good player there,
transferred to South Carolina in the SEC
and had a really good year this year. Um
we just think that um again he's very
young. Um but we think he's a really
good player now with a with a ton of
upside.
>> Yeah. Just 20 years old. That's almost
unheard of, isn't it?
>> Yeah. Kenny Clark like, you know what I
mean? So hopefully it could turn out
that good. But yeah, he's one of the
younger players in the draft and um
again, but very mature young man and
very very intense and and and football
is very important to him. Him being a
great player is very important to him.
So, we think he's going to fit here very
well with our with our team and then our
culture here.
>> You know, seeing the video I've seen on
him, he's not bashful whatsoever about
the rough stuff, right?
>> He'll stick his nose in there.
>> Absolutely. He's uh again he can play
off, he can play press, he'll tackle,
you know. So again, you know, all these
guys are going to have to learn the the
NFL game and what this is all about cuz
it is different what they've
experienced. But we think that his skill
set really does lend itself to be a
pretty good player in this league.
>> In the third round, you make a trade
move up to select Chris Mlullen out of
Missouri defensive tackle.
>> What attracted you to him? Yeah, first
of all, you know, he's 6'4, he's 315
pounds, can stop the run, he holds the
print very, very well. He's a very He
also is a very good pass rusher. He can
play up and down the line, so he's very
versatile, which obviously, as you know,
we like very much. And again, played in
the SEC, played in the league where that
matters. And um so again, he's a young
player, proven already at a very high
level in college, and I think he's going
to be a really good fit here. looks
like, and this is always sometimes, I
think, or maybe it used to be a concern
with the big guys, he's got a good
motor. He does. I mean, he he brings it.
>> Yeah. He plays hard, played a lot of
snaps there. I think he was up over
60ome percent and did everything. He was
one not one of those guys that came off
the field a lot in third downs. He
played a lot and like you said, he could
rush the passer. So, you know,
tremendous upside would be a good fit
for our
>> Have you ever drafted a guy before with
11 in hands? Yeah, [laughter] those I I
I pay money just to look at his hands.
>> Yeah. Interesting enough, we had Shawn
Ryan, right? Shawn Ryan 11. So, yeah,
we've had a few guys here and there that
have gotten to that that level, but
yeah, he's like I said, he's a big man
now and um he's going to add some size
in there and certainly that was
something that was was important to us.
>> Has the draft in general been falling
the right way as far as you're
concerned?
>> Yeah, I think it did for us today. You
know, I think uh the board held up very
well. Well, we had a number of choices
at 52 and then a number of choices
[music] in the third round. I think
certainly with Christopher, we felt that
he was one of those players that we we
felt we needed to go get. Uh not
necessarily because we were for sure
that he was going to get taken.
Certainly, we didn't know that, but we
thought um his value was was right to do
that.
>> I don't know how much you can say, but
can you offer some sort of scouting
report for how you're approaching
tomorrow? Yeah, I think we're just we're
always going to let the board talk to us
a little bit and try to get into the
areas where we think it's strong. Uh
there's a lot of good players left up
there that we really think can help us
and so we'll kind of um you know just
monitor as it goes. But u we won't be
afraid to be aggressive if the right
guys there um and we won't be afraid to
to move down and add picks as well. But
um you know again I think I like I like
our football team right now. I like our
roster. So um you know we're going to
try to add some quality players
tomorrow. We're excited about it. Bottom
line, Gudy, did you get better tonight?
Would you feel that?
>> Yeah, I think again starting with Jaden,
you know, and doing that extension with
him. I mean, that was really important
for us. We got a lot of work to do with,
you know, some extensions as we go um
you know, over the next few months.
That'll be important for us and that was
a good start. And um and certainly the
draft finally, you know, watching 51
guys come off the board before you get
the pick is not something I', you know,
like to do, but um ending up getting a
player like Brandon and Christopher, I
think that was really important for us.
When you go into a draft with Micah
Parsons as your first round draft
choice, do you kind of feel like you're
playing with the house's money a little
bit?
>> Yeah, a little bit. You know, that's I I
told him today that, you know, when it
was our pick at 20, what was supposed to
be our pick at 20, we had his card up,
you know, he's ready to go. But uh um
yeah, certainly looking back on that, no
regrets there. Certainly we uh we that's
one of those things that uh certainly
how he played last year. We're pretty
excited about him coming back.
>> Goody, good luck tomorrow. Thanks for
the time.
>> Thanks, Rock.